MORGAN MCDONALD

STUDENT AT GLASGOW CLYDE COLLEGE

morganmcdee13@outlook.com

- morganmcdonald.co.uk/
- **** 07403315019
- in morganmcdonald13
- norganmcdnald

A Computer Science Programmer qualified to BA degree level who is currently undertaking an additional HNC qualification within Web Engineering, with sights to progress to HND. With a strong attention to detail, also being a great multitasker and problem solver aids in my design and development work. Have teamworking experience from both my educational and professional careers.

Skills

WEB DEV + **PROGRAMMING** SKILLS

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

Python

Java

Django

SASS

jQuery

WordPress

PHP

Vue

WEB DESIGN SKILLS

Figma

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe XD

Adobe After Effects

Education

University of Glasgow

BSc Computer Science 2019

Glasgow Clyde College - Langside

HND Web Engineering 2022

Glasgow Clyde College - Cardonald

HND Computer Science 2017

St Matthew's Academy Aug. 2009 to June 2015

Standard Grades: Maths - 1, Computing - 1, Business -1, Chemistry - 2,

English - 2, Spanish - 2, 2 - History

Int 2: Art - A

Highers: Maths - B, English - B, Computing - B, Business Management - C,

Spanish - C, Art - D

Advanced Higher: Maths - B

Employment

Compass Group UK

Cafe Assistant

Ardrossan, North Ayrshire Nov. 2019 to Current

Sept. 2017 to June 2019

Aug. 2020 to Current

Aug. 2015 to June 2017

Opening and closing up the cafe, preparing food, taking and refilling stock, washing up, serving customers, cleaning and tidying

Domino's Pizza

Delivery Expert

Stevenston, North Ayrshire July 2018 to Nov. 2019

Delivering food, preparing food, making pizzas, taking orders, preparing boxes, refilling stock, washing up, tidying, counting money

Seamill Hydro Hotel

Seamill, North Ayrshire Nov. 2015 to Oct. 2016

Conferencing & Banqueting Staff Bar and table service, cashier work, pouring drinks, taking stock levels, tidying, washing, setting tables, preparing and clearing bar, serving food and clearing tables

Activities

Graphic Design

Self taught in Photoshop, I started an Instagram account for posting some graphics I designed and amassed over 1.5k followers. This led to me getting some one-off clients, for whom I have designed and made Instagram posts, event posters and business cards.

Football

Playing for teams when I was younger and switching to help coaching as I got older, I was involved in football for most of my mouth. Still an avid fan and play with friends when possible.